<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-02-07T04:05:40+00:00</updated><id>https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">What is Art Healing</title><link href="https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/what-is-art-healing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What is Art Healing" /><published>2021-04-10T13:22:16+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-10T13:22:16+00:00</updated><id>https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/what-is-art-healing</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/what-is-art-healing/">&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#introduction&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, art has had a healing function since ancient times. As archaeologists discover and gather more evidence and new sites, Neanderthals created various shapes and sizes of markings on the walls of caves - this is the earliest form of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Packard, humans during this period may have begun using art to psychologically prepare hunters for their long and dangerous hunting expeditions. These cave paintings depicted the fears, hopes, and desires of hunters, and were symbolically offered to their gods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As one of the most developed countries in art therapy, the art therapy industry in the United States has a history of over 80 years. In recent years, universities have gradually incorporated “art therapy” into their discipline and professional scope, as well as the development of “humanistic art therapy” in China. Art therapy has become a truly emerging treatment technology in China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By definition, art therapy is an auxiliary form of psychotherapy that differs from language communication in conventional psychotherapy. It uses creative forms to analyze and explore individual problems through artistic creation. Simply put, it is a way to vent emotions and heal oneself through watching or creating. The art therapy profession spans both art and psychology majors, and the presentation of works is mainly in the form of visual art, manifested in performing arts such as illustration, installation, interactive media, dance, drama, etc. Translate the above paragraph into English&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s2.loli.net/2023/09/20/DYju7w4tChOr9kH.png&quot; alt=&quot;Art Healing Process&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;1300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr style=&quot;border-top: 1px solid #9D9D9D ; color: #9D9D9D ;&quot; class=&quot;endpost&quot; /&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Art Hearling" /><category term="Psychological Design" /><category term="Pressure&amp;Loneliness" /><summary type="html">Introduction Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What is Tech AI</title><link href="https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/what-is-art-tech/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What is Tech AI" /><published>2021-04-10T13:22:16+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-10T13:22:16+00:00</updated><id>https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/what-is-art-tech</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jekyll-typing-artist.vercel.app/blog/what-is-art-tech/">&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#introduction&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#academic-background&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-academic-background&quot;&gt;Academic Background&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#business-background&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-business-background&quot;&gt;Business Background&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#1-major-investments-by-tech-giants&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-1-major-investments-by-tech-giants&quot;&gt;1. Major Investments by Tech Giants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#2-ethical-ai-and-regulation&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-2-ethical-ai-and-regulation&quot;&gt;2. Ethical AI and Regulation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#3-financial-market-reactions&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-3-financial-market-reactions&quot;&gt;3. Financial Market Reactions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) has become an essential part of technological innovation. From self-driving cars to virtual assistants, AI powers the modern world. Among the many domains of AI, fields like Generative AI, Scikit-learn applications, and frameworks like Hugging Face have garnered widespread attention for their transformative capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;academic-background&quot;&gt;Academic Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The foundation of Tech AI is deeply rooted in computer science and mathematics. Early research in AI focused on symbolic reasoning, rule-based systems, and logical decision-making. Over the decades, the integration of machine learning (ML) and deep learning (DL) has reshaped AI into a field capable of mimicking human-like behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.constellationr.com/sites/default/files/uploads/Generative%20AI%20-%20LLMs%20-%20Foundation%20Models%20-%20The%20Future%20of%20Work.png&quot; alt=&quot;Art Healing Process&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;1300&quot; /&gt;
Generative AI, one of the most exciting domains, leverages techniques like neural networks to generate new content such as text, images, and even music. A pivotal breakthrough was the introduction of models like GPT (Generative Pre-trained Transformer) and diffusion-based models like Stable Diffusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Educational institutions have started offering specialized AI programs. For example, Stanford University offers advanced courses in Generative AI and neural networks, while platforms like Hugging Face and Scikit-learn provide developers with powerful tools for AI model deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an emerging discipline, Tech AI spans multiple domains such as computer vision, natural language processing, and reinforcement learning. The presentation of its applications includes innovations in fields like autonomous vehicles, healthcare diagnostics, and personalized education. Tech AI represents the synthesis of computational capabilities and domain-specific insights, transforming how humans interact with technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;business-background&quot;&gt;Business Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tech AI has become a driving force in both industry and academia. For example, companies like OpenAI and Google DeepMind lead the charge in developing AI models that redefine the boundaries of human creativity and problem-solving. Tools like Scikit-learn enable businesses to build predictive models using structured data, while Hugging Face provides state-of-the-art frameworks for deploying large language models (LLMs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-major-investments-by-tech-giants&quot;&gt;1. Major Investments by Tech Giants&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leading technology companies are making substantial investments in AI infrastructure. Alphabet, Google’s parent company, has announced plans to invest $75 billion in AI infrastructure, including servers and data centers, to meet the growing demand for AI services. Similarly, Meta and Microsoft have committed tens of billions of dollars to enhance their AI capabilities.  ￼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A notable development is the rise of DeepSeek, a Chinese AI company that has garnered significant attention for its efficient AI models. DeepSeek’s AI Assistant app has surpassed competitors like ChatGPT in popularity on the iOS App Store in the United States. The company’s ability to develop competitive AI models with fewer resources has been recognized as a potential challenge to the global dominance of American AI models.  ￼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-ethical-ai-and-regulation&quot;&gt;2. Ethical AI and Regulation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus on ethical AI has become increasingly prominent. Businesses that prioritize ethical AI practices are expected to lead in customer trust and loyalty. Additionally, regulatory bodies, particularly in the European Union, are imposing stringent regulations on AI, emphasizing the need for responsible development and deployment.  ￼ ￼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AI’s integration into various industries continues to expand. In marketing, generative AI is becoming a central driver of innovation, enabling more personalized and efficient customer interactions. In sectors like manufacturing and supply chain management, AI is enhancing efficiency and decision-making processes.  ￼ ￼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-financial-market-reactions&quot;&gt;3. Financial Market Reactions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The advancements in AI have also influenced financial markets. Companies like Palantir Technologies have gained favor among investors due to their positive outlook on how cost-effective AI can bolster business operations. The emergence of companies like DeepSeek has led to market volatility, affecting the stock prices of major tech firms.  ￼ ￼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, the AI business landscape in 2025 is characterized by substantial investments from tech giants, the emergence of innovative players like DeepSeek, a heightened focus on ethical practices and regulation, and the pervasive integration of AI across various industries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr style=&quot;border-top: 1px solid #9D9D9D ; color: #9D9D9D ;&quot; class=&quot;endpost&quot; /&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Tech" /><category term="Generative AI" /><category term="Scikit-learn" /><category term="Hugging Face" /><summary type="html">Introduction Introduction Artificial Intelligence (AI) has become an essential part of technological innovation. From self-driving cars to virtual assistants, AI powers the modern world. Among the many domains of AI, fields like Generative AI, Scikit-learn applications, and frameworks like Hugging Face have garnered widespread attention for their transformative capabilities.</summary></entry></feed>